spicymatch.com 2016-11-16

# Privacy policy | SpicyMatch

This Privacy Policy are related to the use of SpicyMatch site, identified by the URL spicymatch.com, owned by "SpicyMatch Ltd." company. For SpicyMatch your privacy is big concern. We have developed this privacy policy to ensure that your privacy is always protected while using our network.

By accessing this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept these terms, please do not access the site.

We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of users who do not use the site in accordance with our Terms of use.

### Access forbidden to minors

The use or viewing of our services by minors is strictly forbidden.

### About SpicyMatch and the information we collect

SpicyMatch is a social network that offers its users a set of tools to get in touch with their global community. The network of SpicyMatch can be used by all registered members who are older than 18.

In our online registration form, we ask you to provide a few information such as name, email address and sex. These data are accessible at any time and can be changed or updated (except for your sex and your profile nickname) accessing "Edit your profile" link.

At your discretion, you can add more details about you. Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself such as your religious denomination, ethnic background, sexual preferences, physical and mental health details. While you may voluntarily provide this information to us when you create your Profile, including your sexual preferences and ethnic background, there is no requirement to do so. Please remember that photographs or any video clips that you post may reveal these kinds of sensitive personal data. Where you do upload and choose to tell us sensitive information about yourself, you are explicitly consenting us to process your information and make this visible to other users, accordingly to this Privacy Policy.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on the site or other materials from you, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect information about you coming from other users in our department that deals with complaints.

### Information collected automatically

During the use of our website, we automatically track certain information such as your IP and email addresses. Various sites use this kind of information for analysis. If you decide to disclose your personal information using any of our communication tools, such as electronic messaging, you do so at your full responsibility.

#### Cookies & similar technologies

SpicyMatch uses cookies (text files small in size that are stored on your device while browsing). Cookies can be stored permanently on your device and have a variable duration (persistent cookies), or they can unsubscribe by closing the browser or even be of limited duration (session cookies). Cookies can be installed by SpicyMatch.com or can be installed from other websites (third-party cookies).

Cookies installed by SpicyMatch.com are mainly technical: they are used to improve the browsing experience, for statistical purposes and for security.

The third-party cookies are used for statistical purposes or for the possible interaction with other portals or social networks.

Cookies can be completely disabled in your browser. In such cases, however, some SpicyMatch.com functionalities may be inaccessible and/or operate incorrectly. For more information on how to delete and / or control cookies on your browser, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Location

Using SpicyMatch.com applications with location services SpicyMatch.com may collect and process information about your current position. This data is processed anonymously in a form that does not identify you personally and used only to facilitate the use of certain functions of the application based on geolocation. Location services can be enabled or disabled by the user at any time by going to the settings of your device (for more information please consult the guide of your device).

### Use of your information

The personal information of our users are used by SpicyMatch to statistically analyze site usage, to verify law respect, to improve our content and our services, and customize contents and style of the site at your needs. We may also use your personal information to send you information that might be of interest to you, such as targeted banners and promotions. We believe that this will allow us to improve both our site, and your online experience and to meet your expectations. We use personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of use.

You can choose to receive emails from us regarding new message notifications, or for other reasons related to the use of the site. This feature can be turned on and off through the "Notifications settings".

### Disclosure of your information

We do not disclose any of your personal information to third parties.

SpicyMatch collaborates actively with all the requests received from law enforcement agencies or third parties in relation to the respect of other's rights, including intellectual property. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by the competent authorities, if we believe that communication is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with any obligations relating to judicial proceedings in which is involved our site.

### Use of information relating to other users

You are not allowed to use any information about other users for commercial purposes, spamming, harassment or threats. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who thus use the information relating to other users, or otherwise violate our Terms of use.

### Inactivity

In case you have not logged on to the site for a period longer than 180 days, your account may be deleted after a process of cleaning and tidying of our databases.

### Control of your password

You may not disclose your password to others or share it with anyone. If, nevertheless, have no longer the exclusive control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information, with the result that you might even see you involved in legal proceedings against you. So, if you lose control of your password, you should immediately change it.

### Reviewing and changing your information

Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personal information including:

  1. Your contact email address;
  2. Your profile, photographs, and videos;
  3. Your city, region, and country of residence;
  4. Your password.

Please promptly update your information if it changes by signing-in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information.

You are entitled to exercise a right of access to personal information about yourselves by asking for a copy of the information we hold about you.

Any comments or queries are welcomed by us, so please feel free to send a message to our helpdesk, including information for the editing your information and configurations.

### Security

SpicyMatch has implemented security measures to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Security measures, such as secured servers using firewalls, are used to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at SpicyMatch work hard to ensure your secure use of our site.

### Can I deactivate or delete my profile?

SpicyMatch users have the following choices to delete their profile from our database:

  1. Send a message to our helpdesk;
  2. Sign in with your password and delete your profile.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SpicyMatch reserves the right to change this Privacy policy at any time and without notice, so be sure to check this Privacy policy regularly. If we make material changes to this Privacy policy, we will notify you here, by email or through notice on our homepage.
